Get ready for a second Rush!
Rush Hour 2 is a action, comedy, crime film directed by Brett Ratner.
It's vacation time for Carter as he finds himself alongside
Lee in Hong Kong wishing for more excitement.
While Carter wants to party and meet the ladies, Lee is out to track down a Triad gang
lord who may be responsible for killing two men at the American Embassy.
Things get complicated as the pair stumble onto a counterfeiting plot.
The boys are soon up to their necks in fist fights
and life-threatening situations.
A trip back to the U.S.
may provide the answers about the bombing, the counterfeiting, and
the true allegiance of sexy customs agent Isabella.
Yan Naing Lee, played by Jackie Chan.
James Carter, played by Chris Tucker.
Ricky Tan, played by John Lone.
Isabella Molina, played by Roselyn Sánchez.
Hu Li, played by Zhang Ziyi.
Steve Reign, played by Alan King.
Rush Hour 2 is a 2001 American buddy cop action comedy film
directed by Brett Ratner and written by Jeff Nathanson.
A sequel to Rush Hour (1998), it is the second installment in the Rush Hour franchise and
stars Jackie Chan and Chris Tucker reprising their roles from the first film.
The story follows Hong Kong Police Force (HKPF) Chief Inspector Lee (Chan) and Los Angeles Police Department (LAPD) Detective
James Carter (Tucker), who go to Hong Kong on vacation only to be thwarted by a murder case involving two U.S.
customs agents after a bombing at the American embassy.
Lee suspects that the crime is linked to the Triad crime lord Ricky Tan (Lone).
This film was filmed in Hong Kong, Los Angeles & Las Vegas.
Rush Hour 2 opened on August 3, 2001, to generally mixed reviews.
The film was a commercial success, grossing $347.4 million worldwide,
making it the highest-grossing film in the franchise.
It also became the year's fifth-highest-grossing film domestically in the United States,
as well as the second-highest-grossing PG-13-rated film in that market.
A sequel, Rush Hour 3, was released on August 10, 2007.
The film explores themes of martial arts, los angeles, california,
criminal investigation, interracial friendship, buddy cop.
The tone is lighthearted.